<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scene on Jaboury Ghazoul</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scene on Jaboury Ghazoul</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low&#xA;bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a&#xA;large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter&#xA;abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by&#xA;the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the&#xA;velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who&#xA;had stolen in, the usher stopped him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-scale plant-pollinator network dynamics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project aims to understand the effect of land use change in shaping the structure of plant-pollinator interaction networks in the coffee agroforestry of India. Using a combination of advanced landscape mapping, observational studies, pollen metabarcoding, and eDNA approaches, we aim to understand how the plant-pollinator network dynamics are affected by local and landscape level transitions in the land use. Also, the plausible causal pathways affecting the structure of plant pollinator interaction networks are assessed. The outcomes of this work can inform better land management strategies to restore biodiversity, ecosystem productivity and resilience, and sustainable agricultural production.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
