<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ananke: a Hugo Theme on Jaboury Ghazoul</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ananke: a Hugo Theme on Jaboury Ghazoul</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of&#xA;this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on&#xA;by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to&#xA;listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined&#xA;to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on&#xA;the part of the public. This gleam of hope acquired fresh life, when he&#xA;saw Quasimodo, Coppenole, and the deafening escort of the pope of the&#xA;procession of fools quit the hall amid great uproar. The throng rushed&#xA;eagerly after them. “Good,” he said to himself, “there go all the&#xA;mischief-makers.” Unfortunately, all the mischief-makers constituted the&#xA;entire audience. In the twinkling of an eye, the grand hall was empty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion. It was settled that each candidate, man or woman (for it was possible to choose a female pope), should, for the sake of leaving the impression of his grimace fresh and complete, cover his face and remain concealed in the chapel until the moment of his appearance. In less than an instant, the chapel was crowded with competitors, upon whom the door was then closed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low&#xA;bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a&#xA;large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter&#xA;abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by&#xA;the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the&#xA;velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who&#xA;had stolen in, the usher stopped him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIMBERHAUS: Climate-smart solutions for use of wood in the construction sector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soil Greenhouse Gas Emissions in Restored Landscapes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Globally, forest restoration is promoted as a means of mitigating greenhouse gas emissions by storing carbon in new forests. The Scottish Government has a policy to substantially increase woodland cover in part motivated by its ambitious 2045 net-zero carbon target. New woodlands are consequently being established in the Scottish Highlands, yet these uplands have extensive organic-rich soils that already store 1.7 billion tonnes of carbon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project will explore how new woodlands on organic-rich soils in Scotland affect soil microbial communities and greenhouse gas (carbon dioxide, methane, and nitrous oxide) emissions through the mineralisation of stored organic matter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-scale plant-pollinator network dynamics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project aims to understand the effect of land use change in shaping the structure of plant-pollinator interaction networks in the coffee agroforestry of India. Using a combination of advanced landscape mapping, observational studies, pollen metabarcoding, and eDNA approaches, we aim to understand how the plant-pollinator network dynamics are affected by local and landscape level transitions in the land use. Also, the plausible causal pathways affecting the structure of plant pollinator interaction networks are assessed. The outcomes of this work can inform better land management strategies to restore biodiversity, ecosystem productivity and resilience, and sustainable agricultural production.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the shortcode to make it work. Check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://formspree.io/&#34;&gt;Formspree&lt;/a&gt; for a simple, free form service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;form class=&#34;black-80 sans-serif&#34; accept-charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34; action=&#34;https://example.com&#34; method=&#34;POST&#34; role=&#34;form&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34;  for=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Your Name&lt;/label&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; id=&#34;name&#34; name=&#34;name&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn&#34;  required placeholder=&#34; &#34;  aria-labelledby=&#34;name&#34;/&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34; for=&#34;email&#34;&gt;Email Address&lt;/label&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; id=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn&#34;  required placeholder=&#34; &#34;  aria-labelledby=&#34;email&#34;/&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;requirements f6 gray glow i ph3 overflow-hidden&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;      An email address is required.&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34; for=&#34;message&#34;&gt;Message&lt;/label&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;textarea id=&#34;message&#34; name=&#34;message&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn h4&#34; aria-labelledby=&#34;message&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;input class=&#34;db w-100 mv2 white pa3 bn hover-shadow hover-bg-black bg-animate bg-black&#34; type=&#34;submit&#34; value=&#34;Send&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/form&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaboury Ghazoul</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Victor_Hugo-Hunchback.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881)&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an ecologist working with complex socio-ecological systems, I aim to understand how ecological processes and landscape dynamics are shaped by the decisions that people make. This means talking to people to understand their values and perspectives, and hence the reasons for the decisions they make.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
